secret_script.txt
Digital communication witnesses a noticeable and continuous development in many applications in the Internet.
"Hence, secure communication sessions must be provided.The security of data transmitted across a global network has turned into a key factor on the network performance measures. In today ·s world, data is increasing day-by-day in every sector like medical sector, banking sector, industrial sec tor etc. Some of them are sensitive dataset for clients and others users."
